

As an Interior Designer, the one thing that has always intrigued me is the process of transforming ideas into actual spaces. Along with being creative and enthusiastic, I am inclined towards making appealing, comforting and safer environment for users.

The most relatable quote I've read after been working in the field for almost 3 years is, "Most clients know they need designers. Very few know what to ask them."

I believe it to be true as most times the client can only tell what they want after they see it, and I've managed to learn to ask the right questions and understand their problems. As designers, our job is to provide creative solutions. Once we are able to do that, the design process gets easier for everyone.

EDUCATION

INTERIOR DESIGN SPECIALISATION - 2022

London School of Trends

B.Sc IN INTERIOR DESIGN - 2021

Inter National Institute of Fashion Design

INTERMEDIATE EDUCATION - 2018

St. Anselm's North City School

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

BUNGALOW DESIGN

Conceptualisation - Sem II

FURNITURE DESIGN

Form & Function - Sem III

RESTAURANT DESIGN

Functionality of Space - Sem IV

CO-WORKING COFFEE SHOP DESIGN

Design Process - Sem V

APARTMENT DESIGN

Research on COVID-19 Habitability Situation - Sem V

OFFICE DESIGN

Understanding and implementing specific requirements - Sem VI

EXPERIENCE

SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGING INTERN AT MOHNA & CO.

March 2020 - August 2020

INTERIOR DESIGN INTERN AT JOGI DESIGN STUDIO, JAIPUR

April 2021 - October 2021

JR INTERIOR DESIGN AT TATVASTU, JAIPUR

February 2022 - Present

LIVPRENUER DESIGNER AT LIVSPACE, JAIPUR

February 2022 - Present

SOFT SKILLS

3

Communication & Presentation Skills Eye for Details Quick Learner

Adaptive & Relation Builder

Punctual

Problem Solver

DESIGN SKILLS

Concept Development

Design Thinking

Technical Knowledge

Furniture Design

3D Visualisation

Drafting & Rendering

Material Handling & Selections

Execution Skill

Photography

SOFTWARE SKILLS

AutoCAD	
SketchUp	
Enscape	
3Ds MAX	
Adobe Photoshop	
Adobe Illustrator	
Adobe InDesign	
Microsoft Office	

ACHIEVEMENTS

Volunteered at Rajasthan Heritage Week | October 2018

Residential Upgradation Course, INIFD Bangkok | December 2018

Participated in Lakme Launchpad - Set Design | March 2019

Interview at CNBC | April 2019

Participated in Lime Constuction Workshop, Momasar | October 2019

Participated in Inception of Jai Singh's Metropolis | November 2019

Workshop Achievement in Biophilic Design by Ar. Monica Khosla of KHAM Consulatants | November 2019

Volunteered at WAFA India | March 2020